

Shubham Srivastava

Sr. Software Engineer

Full Stack Developer (MERN)

Advanced through promotions with 3+ years experience, culminating in present senior-level role overseeing firm's software development activities. Provide cradle-to-grave oversight of software project management, leading the research, design, development, documentation and rollout of enterprise applications.

Email - shubhamda111@gmail.com

Current loc - Mumbai, India

LinkedIn - linkedin.com/in/shubham-srivastava-

258876159

Contact - 9695882929 / 8368858039

About - shubham srivastava/me

Github - github.com/srivastavshubham

WORK EXPERIENCE

Coalescence Technologies

Mumbai, India

Sr. Software Engineer (Full Stack)

11/2021 - Present

Jr. Software Developer 09/2020 – 11/2021

Work History

Designed dozens of software solutions driving continuous improvement to processes, systems, work flow and customer responsiveness.

Mentored development teams as a lead developer in Web and Apps developemnt best practices.

Developed web application using React.js and Node.js (MERN stack).

Worked in Back-end Development, made REST APIs using Node.js and Express and Python and done integration in UI.

Worked on the development and implementation of Blockchain technologies.

Trancis Consulting Services Gurugram, India

Software Engineer

03/2020 - 08/2020

Work History

Designed the front end using HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and ES6 features.

Skilled in leading frameworks as React JS to build high-quality, scalable and reusable components and Front-end solution.

Leveraged React JS resources for all data access, encapsulating URL's and standardizing data access interfaces.

SKILLS



EXPERTISE

- Web/App Development
- Project Management
- Team Building & Leadership
- Release Management

LANGUAGES

HINDI

Full Professional Proficiency

ENGLISH

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Coding | Video Gaming

Internet Surfing

Playing Cricket

EDUCATION

| Master of Computer Application (MCA) Galgotias College of Engineering and Technology, Greater Noida (Abdul Kalam Technical University, Lucknow) CGPA – 8.09, Percentage – 80.60 % | 2020 |
|---|------|
| Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA) Chhatrapati Shahu Ji Maharaj University, Kanpur Percentage – 63 % | 2017 |
| 12 th Udaya Public School, Ayodhya Percentage – 62 % | 2013 |
| 10 th St. Xavier's High School , Basti Percentage – 50 % | 2011 |

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all particulars given above are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Shubham Srivastava